Hello to all of you, in this video I will
tell you how to fill the Pre-Modern Form of Oriental Insurance Company Limited, so how to download this platform, so first of all
you do
not have the facility to claim online, for this you have to
fill this form and take it to the nearest branch,
after that you are
appointed a survey or you can
also call your development officer and
extend the server, okay so this is the phone, let me
tell you the method of downloading, how to
download, so first of all you open Google
Chrome, after going to Google Chrome,
write Oriental Insurance
Tonic, after this the site will open,
go to this site
and after that the home page will open,
download is shown on the home page,
when you click on download,
like you will click on download, you will
scratch like this, it will be visible in it,
download claim form, click on download film,
then you will start directly from
Pune, okay see here
you have to do many steps ahead in this work, but
our work is to download the motor insurance claim
form and its motor in
motor policy  If you want to take it, you should download it, then
how will the downloading app be done
and print this form,
after printing it, it will
also be the address of the person who has
taken the policy, okay, here
we will
enter the policy number, the policy number 15, okay,
army number to z, you
do not enter the number for entering these friend number from when to when,
we will enter the plumber, which is the work of the office people,
okay, after that here we are
asking for the name, that is, what is the name of the policy holder, what is
his address, what is his mobile number, we will
enter it, okay now after that see
here, but they are asking, that is,
which company is the manufacturer of the player and
his hair, that is, suppose your
car is Tata Sumo, then we will give you Kali Din Yaar Totally
and the model mileage is 2004, so let's write it
here 2012, okay, by doing Tata Tata, okay,
we will write that, enter the engine number, chassis
number, vehicle number is
also there in the war vehicle number, write it,
after that they are asking whether
that option is working properly  If the condition is
yes then it should be done but if not then note it down.
Now after that the purpose was visible
been used time friends, for what
purpose do you use the vehicle, if it is private or
commercial use then private tutor will give it in
and if it is commercial then CB will write it for commercial
use, okay now after that if there was inheritance
about trailer test or not then
we will write it and if not then we will
not write it, okay now after that we will
click on whether there is decided cartage or not,
after that additional information is being
asked from commercial vehicle commer, that
means if it is for track from trade market then
register but they have to write how many
grams of sugar have to be written in fronted, then
after that they will check the stop good, whatever your case like, what is the
weight of all, nature of permit,
what type of permit is it and if we look at the nature of goods
that were being carried then
what type is it, after that when that ace is
registered and okay after that these tractor
trailers have to be written
and this is Yagnik bus, this is taxi vehicle
then how much money  It is
okay to write about the implications and the number of passengers for which the
permit is to be issued, then this will be done,
after that you have to
write the name of the driver, the owner, that is, who was driving the vehicle at the time of the accident,
his address, and if the
owner is Ali Khan, then we will next do it, and
if your driver is driving for a fee, if he is a
pet driver, then we will pay for him,
okay, if your brother is driving, your
father is driving, or if he is
also offering some face, then the police will inform you about his
relative, okay, after that, on
this, the driver, how old has he been an employee, that is, for
how many
years has the driver been working nearby,
after that write the driving license number,
so the authority means from where was his driving
license issued, from Raipur
tehsil, whatever it is,
like CG-04 license number, then
it means that it is only
of Raipur district, there is no charge here,
Punya Mahasamund Today topic, it means that
his license is being developed,
after that when the license is temporary or permanent, that is,
his license is  It is temporary that the
permit has to be written now, okay, if there is any
kind of endorsement, then it has to be written,
after that I am asking whether today I have been involved in an accident,
if before that and if I have been involved in
any accident, then it has to be
written, okay, the
police will accuse me of that, but it is the
UK accident, date and time
digits, all mean the
date and time of the car accident, please click on the place, at
what speed was the car,
how did the car happen, where was it going, and in this
way you have to write it, and if
you have
shifted your car to a garage, then
you have to make a statement from the garage owner, the
main owner of the garage
gives you a statement that there is
this damage in this car, this much will be the expense, keep
it, you have to fill the details here, how much is the
damage, you will enter it, okay, and
which owner of the car, enter his name, address and
mobile number, if there is any
third party damage in that car, if there is any
property damage, then this time
you will have to enter the complete details,
okay,
I am in Indore to drive Urea  The driver will have to
remove you from the gift during these days, if there is
any witness during the accident,
you heard, take him, okay, write his name
and if there is a police complaint, then
put the police complaint here and put the FIR
number and the address of the police station, if the
car was stolen by a thief, put the
day and date here, the place where it was
stolen, how it was stolen, okay, put all this
and take the police station here, under which police station the
car was stolen and the FIR
number and diary,
so here
you have to sign here,
after doing all this,
you will have to take photocopy of everything, photocopy of license, photocopy of
Aadhar card,
PAN card and bank passbook copy,
you will take photocopy of all this along with this original
form and the enlistment which will be given by the planet, the
statement which will be made by the planet,
you will take it and go to your nearest branch and
submit all these things, the person
submitting it will fool you and
now the next process will come, so how did you like this video
Yogi, if you liked it then good, like
or share it, so our
channel  Subscribe to Thank You